Arun Vasudevan

Web Developer / Designer



**** +91 7736633673

🔀 arunvasudevan02@gmail.com

• Alappuzha, Kerala

in arun vasudevan

vasudev-arun

I am a highly motivated and skilled web developer and designer with a passion for creating beautiful and functional websites. I am confident that I can use my skills and experience to make a significant contribution to your company.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- C/CPP
- Javascript
- Canva
- Figma
- Github
- Python
- JavaScript

LANGUAGES

- English
- Malayalam
- Hindi

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cold Brew Tech

Community executive program Intern 06/2020 – 07/2021 | Bangalore Completed 1 year of the Community Executive program from Cold Brew Tech. During this internship, I gained the knowledge to maintain a relationship with users and to improve their experience.

Keltron Kerala

Intership On IoT

07/2018 - 07/2018 | Thrissur, India

Completed a 1-week internship on Internet of Things from Keltron Thrissur. During this internship, I gained knowledge of IoT and Its application.

PROJECTS

Tindog 🛮

Alternative of Tinder

2023

Build using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap; Completely responsive webpage.

Added Carousel function.

Calculator [7]

Build this calculator Using JavaScript, CSS, and HTML.

Used Javascript for giving functionality.

Cafe Menu 🛮

A menu card for cafe

Build this cafe menu card using HTML and CSS. Completely responsive webpage

EDUCATION

B.Tech In ECE

KTU

2017 - 2021

Plus two CS

SNHSS Sreekandeswaram

2015 - 2017

SSLC

SNHS Sreekandesram

2015

CERTIFICATIONS

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) ☑

19 hours Course provided by the University of Michigan.

Google Devops Certification

Completed 36 of Dev-Ops Course By Google